<resources>
    <string name="app_name">LostAndFound</string>

    <string name="add_thing">Add Thing</string>
    <string name="find_thing">Find Thing</string>

    <string name="hint_email">email address</string>
    <string name="hint_password">password</string>
    <string name="hint_first_name">first name</string>
    <string name="hint_last_name">last name</string>
    <string name="login">login</string>
    <string name="link_to_login">Already registered. Sign in Me!</string>
    <string name="signup_a_new_account">Sign up for a new account!</string>
    <string name="sign_out">sign out</string>
    <string name="forgot_password">Forgot Your Password? Click here!</string>
    <string name="share">share</string>

    <string name="hint_thing_title">Title</string>
    <string name="hint_thing_description">Description</string>

    <string name="select_thing_photo">Add a photo about your stuff!</string>
    <string name="publishing_progress">Publishing Your Thing</string>
    <string name="publishing_progress_description">Your thing is getting uploaded. Wait a few seconds...</string>

    <string name="found_keys">Keys found on Aigburth Road, Liverpool, between the Maccies and the garage. It’s got two keyrings on as well but I’ve covered them up for the owner to identify.</string>
    <string name="found_ring">Was found at willy’s car wash, near the dog wash side in blacks beach.
Sterling silver ring, has one stone missing and engraving on the inside (must be able to identify what it says!)
Would love to find the owner.</string>
    <string name="lost_cat">Please help get our little baby back to us. Missing since December 20th from Thornton Curtis near Ulceby in North Lincolnshire and only a kitten with little experience of the outdoors.
If you have any information about her or have found her please contact me on 07912 222548 or 07989 150888, she is missed more than I can describe. Please help!</string>
    <string name="lost_donkey">This little donkey escaped from a field in Shildon, County Durham on the morning of December 20th and has unfortunately been hit by a car.
He has a leg injury and is receiving medical treatment but we need your help to track down his owner.
Come on folks it’s Christmas and we need to get this little fellow safely back in his stable before the big day!
Anyone with information about his owner should contact 101.
Thank you</string>

    <string name="google_web_client_id">1074777416292-6a73597ab06se6j88i8lc2pm78ttq70q.apps.googleusercontent.com</string>
</resources>
